oasap.com 2018-12-25

# Privacy Policy - Oasap High Street Fashion

**PRIVACY POLICY**  
We've instituted policies intended to ensure that your personal information is handled safely and responsibly. We have posted this privacy policy to let you know what kind of information we collect, how it is handled, what choices you have regarding our use of your information and how you may access some of the data you provide to us.

**The Information We Collect**  
Any personal information you provide to us is maintained on secure servers and our internal systems. We collect information when you register online or update your account, log-in, place an order, opt-in to receive our emails, shop online, request a catalog, promotion, or survey. This information may include, but is not limited to, your contact information (for example, your name, email address, billing and shipping addresses and phone number) and your credit card information. The security of your information is very important to us; we do not give or sell any user information to any third party. You play a role in protecting your information as well. Because your password permits access to your personal information, please keep your password secret and do not disclose it to others.

### **Marketing opt-in and opt-out provision**

When you register, you will be given the option to opt-in to subscribe to our regular update service. We will send you email alerts for new products, features, enhancements, special offers, contests, events of interest, and one-off marketing promotions.

At all times, we will offer you the opportunity to unsubscribe out of any service or update to which you have subscribed, if you change your mind. Any email we send you will contain an easy automated unsubscribe link so that you can opt-out of that subscription. Simply follow the indications in the email. ****

**The Use of Information**  
We may use your information for a variety of purposes to:  
Enhance your online shopping experience and serve you better. For example, we may use it to recognize you and welcome you to the site.  
Better direct our marketing and promotional communications. We may use information to determine the types of merchandise and events you may be interested in resulting in sending you offer for discounts or promotions, highlighting new arrivals or site features.  
Maintaining your trust and confidence is a high priority. If you have any concerns about privacy that have not been answered in this policy, please contact us.

### **CONTACTING US**

If you have concerns about this Privacy Policy or our privacy practices in general, contact us at:

Address: 

Hong Kong: Suite 909, 9/F., Two Grand Tower, 625 Nathan Road, Kowloon.

Email: service@oasap.com

Contact Number: +86 25 66012103
